Guide to the William Leonard Albrecht Papers 1880-1968
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Albrecht Furniture Company, 1886-1968; Series I; 47.25 linear feet, 113 oversize volumes, and 3 oversize tubes
  - General Correspondence, 1936-1968; Subseries 4; 30.0 linear feet
    - K, 1939 (Box-folder 30/6)
    - Levin Brothers, 1939 (Box-folder 30/7)
    - L, 1939 (Box-folder 30/8)
    - Mohawk Carpet Mills, 1939 (Box-folder 30/9)
    - M, 1939 (Box-folder 30/10)
    - National Retail Furniture Association, 1939 (Box-folder 30/11)
    - N, 1939 (Box-folder 30/12)
    - O, 1939 (Box-folder 30/13)
    - P, 1939 (Box-folder 30/14)
    - R, 1939 (Box-folder 30/15)
    - Salisbury and Satterlee, 1939 (Box-folder 30/16)
    - S, 1939 (Box-folder 31/1)
    - T, 1939 (Box-folder 31/2)
    - U, 1939 (Box-folder 31/3)
    - V, 1939 (Box-folder 31/4)
    - W, 1939 (Box-folder 31/5)
    - Z, 1939 (Box-folder 31/6)
    - A, 1940 (Box-folder 31/7)
    - A, 1940 (Box-folder 31/8)
    - F. E. Buck, 1940 (Box-folder 31/9)
    - B, 1940 (Box-folder 31/10)
    - B, 1940 (Box-folder 31/11)
    - Charles P. Cochrane Company, 1940 (Box-folder 31/12)
    - Columbia Mills Incorporated, 1940 (Box-folder 32/1)
    - C, 1940 (Box-folder 32/2)
    - D, 1940 (Box-folder 32/3)
    - E, 1940 (Box-folder 32/4)
    - F, 1940 (Box-folder 32/5)
    - Great Falls Chamber of Commerce, 1940 (Box-folder 32/6)
    - G, 1940 (Box-folder 32/7)
    - H, 1940 (Box-folder 32/8)
    - I, 1940 (Box-folder 32/9)
    - J, 1940 (Box-folder 32/10)
    - K, 1940 (Box-folder 33/1)
    - Levin Brothers, 1940 (Box-folder 33/2)
    - Levin Brothers, 1940 (Box-folder 33/3)
    - L, 1940 (Box-folder 33/4)
    - Mohawk Carpet Mills, 1940 (Box-folder 33/5)
    - James E. Murray, 1940 (Box-folder 33/6)
    - M, 1940 (Box-folder 33/7)
    - M, 1940 (Box-folder 33/8)
    - National Furniture Retail Association, 1940 (Box-folder 33/9)
    - N, 1940 (Box-folder 33/10)
    - O, 1940 (Box-folder 34/1)
    - P, 1940 (Box-folder 34/2)
    - Q, 1940 (Box-folder 34/3)
    - Rainbow Hotel, 1940 (Box-folder 34/4)
    - R, 1940 (Box-folder 34/5)
    - Salisbury and Satterlee, 1940 (Box-folder 34/6)
    - S, 1940 (Box-folder 34/7)
    - T, 1940 (Box-folder 34/8)
    - U, 1940 (Box-folder 34/9)
    - V, 1940 (Box-folder 34/10)
    - Burton K. Wheeler, 1940 (Box-folder 34/11)
    - W, 1940 (Box-folder 34/12)
    - W, 1940 (Box-folder 34/13)
    - X-Z, 1940 (Box-folder 34/14)
    - A, 1941 (Box-folder 35/1)
    - B, 1941 (Box-folder 35/2)
    - Charles P. Cochrane Company, 1941 (Box-folder 35/3)
    - Columbia Mills Incorporated, 1941 (Box-folder 35/4)
    - C, 1941 (Box-folder 35/5)
    - D, 1941 (Box-folder 35/6)
    - E, 1941 (Box-folder 35/7)
    - F, 1941 (Box-folder 35/8)
    - Great Falls Chamber of Commerce, 1941 (Box-folder 35/9)
    - G, 1941 (Box-folder 35/10)
    - H, 1941 (Box-folder 36/1)
    - I, 1941 (Box-folder 36/2)
    - J, 1941 (Box-folder 36/3)
    - K, 1941 (Box-folder 36/4)
    - Levin Brothers, 1941 (Box-folder 36/5)
    - L, 1941 (Box-folder 36/6)
    - Mohawk Carpet Mills, 1941 (Box-folder 36/7)
    - James E. Murray, 1941 (Box-folder 36/8)
    - M, 1941 (Box-folder 36/9)
    - N, 1941 (Box-folder 36/10)
    - James F. O'Connor, 1941 (Box-folder 36/11)
    - O, 1941 (Box-folder 36/12)
    - P, 1941 (Box-folder 36/13)
    - Q, 1941 (Box-folder 36/14)
    - Rainbow Hotel, 1941 (Box-folder 36/15)
    - Jeannette Rankin, 1941 (Box-folder 36/16)
    - R, 1941 (Box-folder 36/17)
    - Salisbury and Satterlee, 1941 (Box-folder 36/18)
    - S, 1941 (Box-folder 37/1)
    - T, 1941 (Box-folder 37/2)
    - U, 1941 (Box-folder 37/3)
    - V, 1941 (Box-folder 37/4)
    - W, 1941 (Box-folder 37/5)
    - X-Z, 1941 (Box-folder 37/6)
    - A, 1942 (Box-folder 37/7)
    - B, 1942 (Box-folder 37/8)
    - Charles P. Cochrane Company, 1942 (Box-folder 37/9)
    - Columbia Mills Incorporation, 1942 (Box-folder 37/10)
    - C, 1942 (Box-folder 37/11)
    - D, 1942 (Box-folder 37/12)
    - E, 1942 (Box-folder 37/13)
    - F, 1942 (Box-folder 37/14)
    - Great Falls Chamber of Commerce, 1942 (Box-folder 37/15)
    - G, 1942 (Box-folder 37/16)
    - H, 1942 (Box-folder 37/17)
    - I, 1942 (Box-folder 38/1)
    - J, 1942 (Box-folder 38/2)
    - K, 1942 (Box-folder 38/3)
    - Levin Brothers, 1942 (Box-folder 38/4)
    - L, 1942 (Box-folder 38/5)
    - M, 1942 (Box-folder 38/6)
    - N, 1942 (Box-folder 38/7)
    - O, 1942 (Box-folder 38/8)
    - P, 1942 (Box-folder 38/9)
    - Q, 1942 (Box-folder 38/10)
    - R, 1942 (Box-folder 38/11)
    - Salisbury and Satterlee, 1942 (Box-folder 38/12)
    - S, 1942 (Box-folder 38/13)
    - T, 1942 (Box-folder 38/14)
    - U, 1942 (Box-folder 38/15)
    - V, 1942 (Box-folder 38/16)
    - W, 1942 (Box-folder 38/17)
    - X-Z, 1942 (Box-folder 38/18)
    - A, 1943 (Box-folder 38/19)
    - B, 1943 (Box-folder 38/20)
    - Charles P. Cochrane Company, 1943 (Box-folder 39/1)
    - Columbia Mills Incorporated, 1943 (Box-folder 39/2)
    - C, 1943 (Box-folder 39/3)
    - D, 1943 (Box-folder 39/4)
    - D, 1943 (Box-folder 39/5)
    - F, 1943 (Box-folder 39/6)
    - Great Falls Chamber of Commerce, 1943 (Box-folder 39/7)
    - G, 1943 (Box-folder 39/8)
    - H, 1943 (Box-folder 39/9)
    - I, 1943 (Box-folder 39/10)
    - J, 1943 (Box-folder 39/11)
    - K, 1943 (Box-folder 39/12)
    - Levin Brothers, 1943 (Box-folder 39/13)
    - L, 1943 (Box-folder 39/14)
    - M, 1943 (Box-folder 39/15)
    - N, 1943 (Box-folder 39/16)
    - O, 1943 (Box-folder 39/17)
    - P, 1943 (Box-folder 39/18)
    - R, 1943 (Box-folder 39/19)
    - Salisbury and Satterlee, 1943 (Box-folder 39/20)
    - S, 1943 (Box-folder 39/21)
    - T, 1943 (Box-folder 39/22)
    - U, 1943 (Box-folder 39/23)
    - V, 1943 (Box-folder 39/24)
    - W, 1943 (Box-folder 39/25)
    - A, 1944 (Box-folder 40/1)
    - F. E. Buck, 1944 (Box-folder 40/2)
    - B, 1944 (Box-folder 40/3)
    - Charles P. Cochrane Company, 1944 (Box-folder 40/4)
    - Columbia Mills Incorporated, 1944 (Box-folder 40/5)
    - Curtis Sales Company, 1944 (Box-folder 40/6)
    - D, 1944 (Box-folder 40/7)
    - E, 1944 (Box-folder 40/8)
    - F, 1944 (Box-folder 40/9)
    - Great Falls Chamber of Commerce, 1944 (Box-folder 40/10)
    - G, 1944 (Box-folder 40/11)
    - H, 1944 (Box-folder 40/12)
    - I, 1944 (Box-folder 40/13)
    - J, 1944 (Box-folder 40/14)
    - K, 1944 (Box-folder 40/15)
    - Levin Brothers, 1944 (Box-folder 40/16)
    - L, 1944 (Box-folder 40/17)
    - M, 1944 (Box-folder 40/18)
    - N, 1944 (Box-folder 40/19)
    - O, 1944 (Box-folder 40/20)
    - P, 1944 (Box-folder 40/21)
    - Q, R, 1944 (Box-folder 40/22)
    - Salisbury and Satterlee, 1944 (Box-folder 41/1)
    - S, 1944 (Box-folder 41/2)
    - T, 1944 (Box-folder 41/3)
    - United States, 1944 (Box-folder 41/4)
    - U, 1944 (Box-folder 41/5)
    - V, 1944 (Box-folder 41/6)
    - W, 1944 (Box-folder 41/7)
    - Y-Z, 1944 (Box-folder 41/8)
    - A, 1945 (Box-folder 41/9)
    - F. E. Buck, 1945 (Box-folder 41/10)
    - B, 1945 (Box-folder 41/11)
    - Columbia Mills Incorporated, 1945 (Box-folder 41/12)
    - C, 1945 (Box-folder 41/13)
    - D, 1945 (Box-folder 41/14)
    - E, 1945 (Box-folder 41/15)
    - F, 1945 (Box-folder 41/16)
    - Great Falls Chamber of Commerce, 1945 (Box-folder 41/17)
    - G, 1945 (Box-folder 41/18)
    - H, 1945 (Box-folder 41/19)
    - I, 1945 (Box-folder 41/20)
    - J, 1945 (Box-folder 41/21)
    - K, 1945 (Box-folder 41/22)
    - Levin Brothers, 1945 (Box-folder 41/23)
    - Lees-Cochrane Company, 1945 (Box-folder 41/24)
    - L, 1945 (Box-folder 41/25)
    - M, 1945 (Box-folder 41/26)
    - N, 1945 (Box-folder 41/27)
    - O, 1945 (Box-folder 41/28)
    - P, 1945 (Box-folder 42/1)
    - Q, 1945 (Box-folder 42/2)
    - Salisbury and Satterlee, 1945 (Box-folder 42/3)
    - S, 1945 (Box-folder 42/4)
    - T, 1945 (Box-folder 42/5)
    - U, 1945 (Box-folder 42/6)
    - V, 1945 (Box-folder 42/7)
    - W, 1945 (Box-folder 42/8)
    - X-Z, 1945 (Box-folder 42/9)
    - A, 1946 (Box-folder 42/10)
    - F. E. Buck, 1946 (Box-folder 42/11)
    - B, 1946 (Box-folder 42/12)
    - Columbia Mills Incorporated, 1946 (Box-folder 42/13)
    - C, 1946 (Box-folder 42/14)
    - D, 1946 (Box-folder 42/15)
    - E, 1946 (Box-folder 42/16)
    - F, 1946 (Box-folder 42/17)
    - Great Falls Chamber of Commerce, 1946 (Box-folder 42/18)
    - G, 1946 (Box-folder 42/19)
    - H, 1946 (Box-folder 42/20)
    - I, 1946 (Box-folder 42/21)
    - J, 1946 (Box-folder 42/22)
    - K, 1946 (Box-folder 43/1)
    - Lees-Cochrane Company, 1946 (Box-folder 43/2)
    - Levin Brothers, 1946 (Box-folder 43/3)
    - L, 1946 (Box-folder 43/4)
    - M, 1946 (Box-folder 43/5)
    - N, 1946 (Box-folder 43/6)
    - O, P, 1946 (Box-folder 43/7)
    - Q, R, 1946 (Box-folder 43/8)
    - Salisbury and Satterlee, 1946 (Box-folder 43/9)
    - S, 1946 (Box-folder 43/10)
    - T, 1946 (Box-folder 43/11)
    - U, 1946 (Box-folder 43/12)
    - V, 1946 (Box-folder 43/13)
    - W, 1946 (Box-folder 43/14)
    - X-Z, 1946 (Box-folder 43/15)
    - A, 1947 (Box-folder 43/16)
    - F. E. Buck, 1947 (Box-folder 43/17)
    - B, 1947 (Box-folder 44/1)
    - Columbia Mills Incorporated, 1947 (Box-folder 44/2)
    - C, 1947 (Box-folder 44/3)
    - D, 1947 (Box-folder 44/4)
    - E, 1947 (Box-folder 44/5)
    - F, 1947 (Box-folder 44/6)
    - Great Falls Chamber of Commerce, 1947 (Box-folder 44/7)
    - G, 1947 (Box-folder 44/8)
    - H, 1947 (Box-folder 44/9)
    - I, 1947 (Box-folder 44/10)
    - J, 1947 (Box-folder 44/11)
    - K, 1947 (Box-folder 44/12)
    - Levin Brothers, 1947 (Box-folder 45/1)
    - L, 1947 (Box-folder 45/2)
    - M, 1947 (Box-folder 45/3)
    - N, 1947 (Box-folder 45/4)
    - O, 1947 (Box-folder 45/5)
    - P, 1947 (Box-folder 45/6)
    - R, 1947 (Box-folder 45/7)
    - Salisbury Company, 1947 (Box-folder 45/8)
    - S, 1947 (Box-folder 45/9)
    - T, 1947 (Box-folder 45/10)
    - U, 1947 (Box-folder 45/11)
    - V, 1947 (Box-folder 45/12)
    - W, 1947 (Box-folder 45/13)
    - X-Z, 1947 (Box-folder 45/14)
    - A, 1948 (Box-folder 45/15)
    - F. E. Buck, 1948 (Box-folder 45/16)
    - B, 1948 (Box-folder 46/1)
    - Columbia Mills Incorporated, 1948 (Box-folder 46/2)
    - C, 1948 (Box-folder 46/3)
    - D, 1948 (Box-folder 46/4)
    - E, 1948 (Box-folder 46/5)
    - F, 1948 (Box-folder 46/6)
    - Great Falls Chamber of Commerce, 1948 (Box-folder 46/7)
    - G, 1948 (Box-folder 46/8)
    - H, 1948 (Box-folder 46/9)
    - I, 1948 (Box-folder 46/10)
    - J, 1948 (Box-folder 46/11)
    - K, 1948 (Box-folder 46/12)
    - James Lees and Sons, 1948 (Box-folder 46/13)
    - Levin Brothers, 1948 (Box-folder 47/1)
    - L, 1948 (Box-folder 47/2)
    - Mohawk Carpet Mills, 1948 (Box-folder 47/3)
    - M, 1948 (Box-folder 47/4)
    - N, 1948 (Box-folder 47/5)
    - O, 1948 (Box-folder 47/6)
    - P, 1948 (Box-folder 47/7)
    - Q, R, 1948 (Box-folder 47/8)
    - Salisbury Company, 1948 (Box-folder 47/9)
    - S, 1948 (Box-folder 47/10)
    - T, 1948 (Box-folder 47/11)
    - U, 1948 (Box-folder 47/12)
    - V, 1948 (Box-folder 47/13)
    - W, 1948 (Box-folder 47/14)
    - X-Z, 1948 (Box-folder 47/15)
    - Albrecht, 1949 (Box-folder 47/16)
    - A, 1949 (Box-folder 47/17)
    - B, 1949 (Box-folder 48/1)
    - Columbia Mills Incorporated, 1949 (Box-folder 48/2)
    - C, 1949 (Box-folder 48/3)
    - Wesley D'Ewart, 1949 (Box-folder 48/4)
    - Dubois and Company, 1949 (Box-folder 48/5)
    - D, 1949 (Box-folder 48/6)
    - Zales N. Ecton, 1949 (Box-folder 48/7)
    - E, 1949 (Box-folder 48/8)
    - F, 1949 (Box-folder 48/9)
    - Great Falls Chamber of Commerce, 1949 (Box-folder 48/10)
    - G, 1949 (Box-folder 48/11)
    - H, 1949 (Box-folder 48/12)
    - I, 1949 (Box-folder 48/13)
    - J, 1949 (Box-folder 48/14)
    - K, 1949 (Box-folder 48/15)
    - James Lees and Sons, 1949 (Box-folder 48/16)
    - Levin Brothers, 1949 (Box-folder 49/1)
    - L, 1949 (Box-folder 49/2)
    - James E. Murray, 1949 (Box-folder 49/3)
    - M, 1949 (Box-folder 49/4)
    - N, 1949 (Box-folder 49/5)
    - O, 1949 (Box-folder 49/6)
    - P, 1949 (Box-folder 49/7)
    - R, 1949 (Box-folder 49/8)
    - Salisbury Company, 1949 (Box-folder 49/9)
    - S, 1949 (Box-folder 49/10)
    - T, 1949 (Box-folder 49/11)
    - U, 1949 (Box-folder 49/12)
    - V, 1949 (Box-folder 49/13)
    - W, 1949 (Box-folder 49/14)
    - Y, 1949 (Box-folder 49/15)
    - Albrecht, 1950 (Box-folder 49/16)
    - A, 1950 (Box-folder 49/17)
    - B, 1950 (Box-folder 50/1)
    - Charlotte Chair Company, 1950 (Box-folder 50/2)
    - Columbia Mills Incorporated, 1950 (Box-folder 50/3)
    - Curtis Sales Company, 1950 (Box-folder 50/4)
    - C, 1950 (Box-folder 50/5)
    - Wesley D'Ewart, 1950 (Box-folder 50/6)
    - Dubois and Company, 1950 (Box-folder 50/7)
    - D, 1950 (Box-folder 50/8)
    - E, 1950 (Box-folder 50/9)
    - F, 1950 (Box-folder 50/10)
    - Grand Rapids Chair Company, 1950 (Box-folder 50/11)
    - Great Falls Chamber of Commerce, 1950 (Box-folder 50/12)
    - Great Falls Labor Council, 1950 (Box-folder 50/13)
    - G, 1950 (Box-folder 50/14)
    - H, 1950 (Box-folder 50/15)
    - Imperial Furniture Company, 1950 (Box-folder 50/16)
    - Herbert C. Iske, 1950 (Box-folder 50/17)
    - I, 1950 (Box-folder 51/1)
    - Johnson-Carper Furniture Company, 1950 (Box-folder 51/2)
    - Johnson Furniture Company, 1950 (Box-folder 51/3)
    - J, 1950 (Box-folder 51/4)
    - K, 1950 (Box-folder 51/5)
    - James Lees and Sons, 1950 (Box-folder 51/6)
    - Levin Brothers, 1950 (Box-folder 51/7)
    - Lloyd Manufacturing Company, 1950 (Box-folder 51/8)
    - L, 1950 (Box-folder 51/9)
    - Ralph Morse Furniture Company, 1950 (Box-folder 51/10)
    - Mueller Furniture, 1950 (Box-folder 51/11)
    - M, 1950 (Box-folder 51/12)
    - N, 1950 (Box-folder 51/13)
    - O, 1950 (Box-folder 51/14)
    - Philadelphia Carpet Company, 1950 (Box-folder 51/15)
    - P, 1950 (Box-folder 51/16)
    - Q, 1950 (Box-folder 51/17)
    - R, 1950 (Box-folder 51/18)
    - Salisbury Company, 1950 (Box-folder 51/19)
    - S, 1950 (Box-folder 52/1)
    - T, 1950 (Box-folder 52/2)
    - United States Bedding Company, 1950 (Box-folder 52/3)
    - U, 1950 (Box-folder 52/4)
    - V, 1950 (Box-folder 52/5)
    - W, 1950 (Box-folder 52/6)
    - Albrecht, 1951 (Box-folder 52/7)
    - A, 1951 (Box-folder 52/8)
    - B, 1951 (Box-folder 52/9)
    - Charlotte Chair Company, 1951 (Box-folder 52/10)
    - Columbia Mills Incorporated, 1951 (Box-folder 52/11)
    - Curtis Sales Company, 1951 (Box-folder 52/12)
    - C, 1951 (Box-folder 52/13)
    - Drexel Furniture Company, 1951 (Box-folder 52/14)
    - Dubois and Company, 1951 (Box-folder 52/15)
    - D, 1951 (Box-folder 52/16)
    - E, 1951 (Box-folder 52/17)
    - F, 1951 (Box-folder 52/18)
    - Grand Rapids Chair Company, 1951 (Box-folder 52/19)
    - Great Falls Chamber of Commerce, 1951 (Box-folder 52/20)
    - Great Falls Employer Council, 1951 (Box-folder 52/21)
    - G, 1951 (Box-folder 53/1)
    - H, 1951 (Box-folder 53/2)
    - Imperial Furniture Company, 1951 (Box-folder 53/3)
    - Herbert C. Iske, 1951 (Box-folder 53/4)
    - Johnson-Carper Furniture Company, 1951 (Box-folder 53/5)
    - Johnson Furniture, 1951 (Box-folder 53/6)
    - J, 1951 (Box-folder 53/7)
    - K, 1951 (Box-folder 53/8)
    - James Lees and Sons, 1951 (Box-folder 53/9)
    - Levin Brothers, 1951 (Box-folder 53/10)
    - Lloyd Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box-folder 53/11)
    - L, 1951 (Box-folder 53/12)
    - Ralph Morse Furniture Company, 1951 (Box-folder 53/13)
    - M, 1951 (Box-folder 53/14)
    - N, 1951 (Box-folder 53/15)
    - O, 1951 (Box-folder 53/16)
    - Philadelphia Carpet, 1951 (Box-folder 53/17)
    - P, 1951 (Box-folder 53/18)
    - R, 1951 (Box-folder 53/19)
    - Salisbury Company, 1951 (Box-folder 53/20)
    - S, 1951 (Box-folder 53/21)
    - T, 1951 (Box-folder 53/22)
    - United States Bedding Company, 1951 (Box-folder 53/23)
    - V, 1951 (Box-folder 53/24)
    - W, 1951 (Box-folder 53/25)
    - X-Z, 1951 (Box-folder 53/26)
    - Albrecht, 1952 (Box-folder 54/1)
    - A, 1952 (Box-folder 54/2)
    - B, 1952 (Box-folder 54/3)
    - Charlotte Chair Company, 1952 (Box-folder 54/4)
    - Columbia Mills Inc., 1952 (Box-folder 54/5)
    - C, 1952 (Box-folder 54/6)
    - Wesley D'Ewart, 1952 (Box-folder 54/7)
    - Drexel Furniture Company, 1952 (Box-folder 54/8)
    - Dubois and Company, 1952 (Box-folder 54/9)
    - D, 1952 (Box-folder 54/10)
    - E, 1952 (Box-folder 54/11)
    - F, 1952 (Box-folder 54/12)
    - Grand Rapids Chair Company, 1952 (Box-folder 54/13)
    - Great Falls Chamber of Commerce, 1952 (Box-folder 54/14)
    - Great Falls Employer Council, 1952 (Box-folder 54/15)
    - G, 1952 (Box-folder 54/16)
    - H, 1952 (Box-folder 54/17)
    - Imperial Furniture Company, 1952 (Box-folder 54/18)
    - Herbert C, Iske, 1952 (Box-folder 54/19)
    - J, 1952 (Box-folder 54/20)
    - K, 1952 (Box-folder 54/21)
    - James Lees and Sons, 1952 (Box-folder 54/22)
    - Levin Brothers, 1952 (Box-folder 54/23)
    - Lloyd Manufacturing Company, 1952 (Box-folder 54/24)
    - L, 1952 (Box-folder 54/25)
    - Montana Chamber of Commerce, 1952 (Box-folder 54/26)
    - Ralph Morse Furniture Company, 1952 (Box-folder 54/27)
    - Mueller Furniture Company, 1952 (Box-folder 54/28)
    - M, 1952 (Box-folder 54/29)
    - N, 1952 (Box-folder 55/1)
    - O, 1952 (Box-folder 55/2)
    - P, 1952 (Box-folder 55/3)
    - R, 1952 (Box-folder 55/4)
    - Salisbury Company, 1952 (Box-folder 55/5)
    - S, 1952 (Box-folder 55/6)
    - T, 1952 (Box-folder 55/7)
    - U.S. Bedding Company, 1952 (Box-folder 55/8)
    - U, 1952 (Box-folder 55/9)
    - V, 1952 (Box-folder 55/10)
    - W, 1952 (Box-folder 55/11)
    - Albrecht, 1953 (Box-folder 55/12)
    - A, 1953 (Box-folder 55/13)
    - B, 1953 (Box-folder 55/14)
    - Chamber of Commerce, U.S., 1953 (Box-folder 55/15)
    - Charlotte Chair Company, 1953 (Box-folder 55/16)
    - Columbia Mills Inc., 1953 (Box-folder 55/17)
    - Curtis Sales, 1953 (Box-folder 55/18)
    - C, 1953 (Box-folder 55/19)
    - Drexel Furniture, 1953 (Box-folder 55/20)
    - Dubois and Company, 1953 (Box-folder 55/21)
    - D, 1953 (Box-folder 55/22)
    - E, 1953 (Box-folder 55/23)
    - F, 1953 (Box-folder 55/24)
    - Grand Rapids Chair Company, 1953 (Box-folder 55/25)
    - Great Falls Chamber of Commerce, 1953 (Box-folder 55/26)
    - Great Falls Employers Council, 1953 (Box-folder 55/27)
    - G, 1953 (Box-folder 55/28)
    - H, 1953 (Box-folder 55/29)
    - Imperial Furniture Company, 1953 (Box-folder 55/30)
    - Herbert C. Iske, 1953 (Box-folder 55/31)
    - I, 1953 (Box-folder 55/32)
    - Johnson Furniture Company, 1953 (Box-folder 55/33)
    - J, 1953 (Box-folder 55/34)
    - K, 1953 (Box-folder 55/35)
    - James Lees and Sons, 1953 (Box-folder 56/1)
    - Levin Brothers, 1953 (Box-folder 56/2)
    - Lloyd Manufacturing Company, 1953 (Box-folder 56/3)
    - L, 1953 (Box-folder 56/4)
    - Ralph Morse Furniture Company, 1953 (Box-folder 56/5)
    - Mueller Furniture Company, 1953 (Box-folder 56/6)
    - M, 1953 (Box-folder 56/7)
    - N, 1953 (Box-folder 56/8)
    - O, 1953 (Box-folder 56/9)
    - P, 1953 (Box-folder 56/10)
    - R, 1953 (Box-folder 56/11)
    - Salisbury Company, 1953 (Box-folder 56/12)
    - S, 1953 (Box-folder 56/13)
    - T, 1953 (Box-folder 56/14)
    - U, 1953 (Box-folder 56/15)
    - V, 1953 (Box-folder 56/16)
    - W, 1953 (Box-folder 56/17)
    - Y, 1953 (Box-folder 56/18)
    - Albrecht, 1954 (Box-folder 56/19)
    - A, 1954 (Box-folder 56/20)
    - B, 1954 (Box-folder 56/21)
    - Chamber of Commerce, U.S., 1954 (Box-folder 56/22)
    - Curtis Sales Company, 1954 (Box-folder 57/1)
    - C, 1954 (Box-folder 57/2)
    - Drexel Furniture Company, 1954 (Box-folder 57/3)
    - D, 1954 (Box-folder 57/4)
    - E, 1954 (Box-folder 57/5)
    - Orvin Fjare, 1954 (Box-folder 57/6)
    - F, 1954 (Box-folder 57/7)
    - G, 1954 (Box-folder 57/8)
    - H, 1954 (Box-folder 57/9)
    - Imperial Furniture Company, 1954 (Box-folder 57/10)
    - I, 1954 (Box-folder 57/11)
    - J, 1954 (Box-folder 57/12)
    - K, 1954 (Box-folder 57/13)
    - James Lees and Sons, 1954 (Box-folder 57/14)
    - Levin Brothers, 1954 (Box-folder 57/15)
    - L, 1954 (Box-folder 57/16)
    - Herman Miller Furniture Company, 1954 (Box-folder 57/17)
    - Montana Chamber of Commerce, 1954 (Box-folder 57/18)
    - Montana, 1954 (Box-folder 57/19)
    - Ralph Morse Furniture Company, 1954 (Box-folder 57/20)
    - Mueller Furniture Company, 1954 (Box-folder 57/21)
    - M, 1954 (Box-folder 57/22)
    - N, 1954 (Box-folder 57/23)
    - P, 1954 (Box-folder 57/24)
    - R, 1954 (Box-folder 58/1)
    - Salisbury Company, 1954 (Box-folder 58/2)
    - S, 1954 (Box-folder 58/3)
    - T, 1954 (Box-folder 58/4)
    - U, 1954 (Box-folder 58/5)
    - V, 1954 (Box-folder 58/6)
    - W, 1954 (Box-folder 58/7)
    - Y, 1954 (Box-folder 58/8)
    - Albrecht, 1955 (Box-folder 58/9)
    - A, 1955 (Box-folder 58/10)
    - B, 1955 (Box-folder 58/11)
    - Chamber of Commerce, U.S., 1955 (Box-folder 58/12)
    - Curtis Sales Company, 1955 (Box-folder 58/13)
    - C, 1955 (Box-folder 58/14)
    - Drexel Furniture Company, 1955 (Box-folder 58/15)
    - D, 1955 (Box-folder 58/16)
    - E, 1955 (Box-folder 58/17)
    - Orvin Fjare, 1955 (Box-folder 58/18)
    - F, 1955 (Box-folder 58/19)
    - G, 1955 (Box-folder 58/20)
    - H, 1955 (Box-folder 58/21)
    - Imperial Furniture Company, 1955 (Box-folder 58/22)
    - Herbert C. Iske, 1955 (Box-folder 58/23)
    - J, 1955 (Box-folder 59/1)
    - K, 1955 (Box-folder 59/2)
    - James Lees and Sons, 1955 (Box-folder 59/3)
    - Levin Bros, 1955. (Box-folder 59/4)
    - L, 1955 (Box-folder 59/5)
    - Ralph Morse Furniture Company, 1955 (Box-folder 59/6)
    - M, 1955 (Box-folder 59/7)
    - N, 1955 (Box-folder 59/8)
    - O, 1955 (Box-folder 59/9)
    - P, 1955 (Box-folder 59/10)
    - R, 1955 (Box-folder 59/11)
    - Salisbury Company, 1955 (Box-folder 59/12)
    - Spinning Wheel, 1955 (Box-folder 59/13)
    - S, 1955 (Box-folder 59/14)
    - T, 1955 (Box-folder 59/15)
    - U, 1955 (Box-folder 59/16)
    - V, 1955 (Box-folder 59/17)
    - W, 1955 (Box-folder 59/18)
    - Y, 1955 (Box-folder 59/19)
    - Z, 1955 (Box-folder 59/20)
    - Albrecht, 1956 (Box-folder 60/1)
    - A, 1956 (Box-folder 60/2)
    - B, 1956 (Box-folder 60/3)
    - Chamber of Commerce, U.S., 1956 (Box-folder 60/4)
    - C, 1956 (Box-folder 60/5)
    - D, 1956 (Box-folder 60/6)
    - E, 1956 (Box-folder 60/7)
    - F, 1956 (Box-folder 60/8)
    - G, 1956 (Box-folder 60/9)
    - H, 1956 (Box-folder 60/10)
    - Imperial Furniture Company, 1956 (Box-folder 60/11)
    - I, 1956 (Box-folder 60/12)
    - J, 1956 (Box-folder 60/13)
    - K, 1956 (Box-folder 60/14)
    - James Lees and Sons, 1956 (Box-folder 60/15)
    - Levin Brothers, 1956 (Box-folder 60/16)
    - L, 1956 (Box-folder 60/17)
    - Ralph Morse Furniture Company, 1956 (Box-folder 60/18)
    - M, 1956 (Box-folder 60/19)
    - N, 1956 (Box-folder 61/1)
    - O, 1956 (Box-folder 61/2)
    - P, 1956 (Box-folder 61/3)
    - R, 1956 (Box-folder 61/4)
    - Salisbury Company, 1956 (Box-folder 61/5)
    - Spinning Wheel, 1956 (Box-folder 61/6)
    - S, 1956 (Box-folder 61/7)
    - T, 1956 (Box-folder 61/8)
    - U, 1956 (Box-folder 61/9)
    - V, 1956 (Box-folder 61/10)
    - W, 1956 (Box-folder 61/11)
    - Y, 1956 (Box-folder 61/12)
    - Z, 1956 (Box-folder 61/13)
    - Albrecht, 1957 (Box-folder 61/14)
    - A, 1957 (Box-folder 61/15)
    - B, 1957 (Box-folder 61/16)
    - Chamber of Commerce, U.S., 1957 (Box-folder 61/17)
    - C, 1957 (Box-folder 61/18)
    - Drexel Furniture Company, 1957 (Box-folder 61/19)
    - D, 1957 (Box-folder 61/20)
    - E, 1957 (Box-folder 61/21)
    - F, 1957 (Box-folder 61/22)
    - G, 1957 (Box-folder 61/23)
    - H, 1957 (Box-folder 62/1)
    - Imperial Furniture Company, 1957 (Box-folder 62/2)